Dat Tien Pham

28.11.1998 Jukolantie 17 B 12, 45200 Kouvola P. +358 409 3232 78 datpt98@gmail.com

Curriculum Vitae 11/2018





SUMMARY

My name is Dat. I am 19 years old and I'm from Vietnam. I am currently studying at South-Eastern University of Applied Sciences, Kouvola campus. I am a hardworking, passionate and sincere individual. I can get used to different working environments and I am always eager to explore new experiences.



EDUCATION

08.2016 - Now South-Eastern University of Applied Sciences (XAMK), Kouvola campus. Bachelor's Degree of Business Administration Field of study: International Business, GPA: 4.0/5.0 08.2016 - 04.2017 Finnish language course, Kouvolan iltalukio 08.2017 - Now High School for Gifted Students, Hanoi University of 08.2013 - 05.2016 Science, Vietnam Major subjects: Information Technology



EXPERIENCES

06.2018 - 08.2018 Fruits Picker, Tyrvännön Marja ja Vihannes (Tyrväntö) In my university's second-year summer, I applied for the work of

berries picking and labelling as a mean to earn my living and support my study in Finland. The work has not only cultivated my punctuality and commitment skills, but also given me the opportunities to truly experience the work environment as a full-time employee.

06.2017 - 08.2017 Waiter and Cashier, Huahin Thai restaurant (Kouvola)

> I worked as a waiter and cashier at Huahin Thai restaurant. The work has provided me with a lot of new and useful experiences and

outlooks when doing service-oriented tasks.

07.2017 - 08.2017 Ad Dealer, Jakelusuora Oy (Kouvola) My job included distributing advertisements, newsletters, magazines, and product samples to every home within a distribution network during required time.

LANGUAGES

X

IT - SKILLs

English Level C1, excellent Finnish Level B1, average Vietnamese Level C2, native

MS Office Excellent
Adobe Photoshop Average
HTML5/CSS3 Good
Javascript/REACT Average
Email Good

CERTIFICATES

03.2017 Hygiene Passport

07.2015 IELTS, overall band score: 7.5

INTERESTS

Reading, Music, Movies, Ice Hockey, Badminton, Bowling, Technology.